SEOJEONG JOO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER
UX / UI DESIGNER

DETAILS



021-0246-5051



sjoo8503@gmail.com



Auckland CBD

New Zealand



linkedin.com/in/sj85/



github.com/sjoo8503

SKILLS

HTML & CSS / SCSS

JavaScript

PHP

LANGUAGES

Korean - Native

English - Fluent

REFERENCE

Simon Folkerts
Yoobee College Tutor
Email: simon.folkerts@
yoobeecolleges.com

PORTFOLIO

https://sjoo8503.github.io/ Portfolio_SJ/

PROFILE

I am a student at Yoobee College, specializing in Web and UX Design. I am a determined person who enjoys working in a team environment, and I am very conscious about using my time wisely. I am very passionate about contributing to real-life engineering situations and widening my views.

OBJECTIVE

- Become a full stack developer
- Gain more front end & back end experiences
- Get familiar with professional development environments
- Experience start and completion cycle of an industry level project
- Challenge myself into the sea of technologies

EDUCATION

YOOBEE COLLEGE

FEB 2022 - DEC 2022 AUCKLAND Diploma in Web and UX/UI Design

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, OSAN DIEGO

SEP 2010 - JUN 2015 SAN DIEGO Bachelor of Chemical Engineering Bachelor of Psychology

EXPERIENCE

VIEVISNAMUH HOSPITAL

JUL 2020 - MAY 2021 SEOUL

Medical Receptionist

- · Handle office and administrative tasks within busy, multi-physician practices
- Process patient check-in/check-out, verifying insurance and collecting third-party claims
- Manage appointment scheduling, patient records, medical billing and financial information

AGAIN

JUL 2016 - JUN 2019 SEOUL

Cafe Manager

- \cdot Manage & allocate jobs among other employees
- · Take care of stocks & financial flows store widely
- Control resources and manage B2B connections for inand out-sourcing

TOOLS

FRAMEWORKS / LIBRARIES

Git / GithubVue.jsMongoDBVS CodeReact.jsMongooseFigmaBootstrapExpress.jsAdobe InDesignNode.js

QUALIFICATION

Art Psychology Counselor 1st Class Qualification